<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This document is licensed under the Creative Commons 3.0 BY-NC-ND License
	 available at http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/. -->
<info>
	<type>Widget</type>
	<general>
		<name>ContextMenu</name>
		<tags>
			<tag>widget</tag>
			<tag>right click</tag>
		</tags>
		<shortDesc>A menu shown with a right click.</shortDesc>
	</general>
	<name>ContextMenu</name>
	<description>The ContextMenu widget appears every time the user clicks the right mouse button. In can handle many options, and every time an option is clicked, the widget sends a signal to the application to make it respond to the action chosen by the user.</description>
	<image>Un menú contextual que aparece al hacer click con el botón derecho del ratón en un área vacía del escritorio.</image>
	<generic_keys>
		<key>
			<name>name</name>
			<desc>Nombre unívoco dado al widget.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>father</name>
			<desc>Nombre de su elemento padre dentro del cual se crea.</desc>
		</key>
	</generic_keys>
	<specific_keys>
		<key>
			<name>mfather</name>
			<desc>Allows to define another father element other than that defined in the 'father' key.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>rfather</name>
			<desc>This parameter is needed to ensure the ContextMenu works correctly under Internet Explorer. Specifies a father element. It can be the same father assigned to the widget.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>searchFather</name>
			<desc>Specifies whether the ContextMenu must be displayed when right click button is pressed anywhere on its father element or not. A value of 1 enables it, while the default value of 0 disables it.</desc>
		</key>
	</specific_keys>
	<methods>
		<method>
			<syntax>void addEvent(string $eventName, string $eventFunc[, string $args = ''])</syntax>
			<desc>Hace que el sistema ejecute un código JavaScript dado cada vez que se produzca un evento en este widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>eventName</name>
					<desc>Nombre del evento JS. Ejemplos: onchange, onmouseup.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>eventFunc</name>
					<desc>Código JavaScript que se ejecutará cada vez que se dispare el evento. El código se ejecutará dentro de una función para que puedan recibirse argumentos.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>args</name>
					<desc>Argumentos pasados a la función del evento.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>addEntry($text, $Ename, $signal [, $params=""])</syntax>
			<desc>Adds a new option to the menu.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>text</name>
					<desc>Displayed text of the option.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>Ename</name>
					<desc>Internal name given to the entry.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>signal</name>
					<desc>Name of the signal sent to the system when the option is clicked.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>params</name>
					<desc>Additional parameters passed when the option sends a signal.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>show(int $noserialize=1)</syntax>
			<desc>Draws the widget in the screen, allowing to serialize the instance in the session.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>noserialize</name>
					<desc>Specifies whether the ContextMenu must be serialized or not. The default value of 1 does not serialize it, while a value of 0 does.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
	</methods>
</info>
