<lang>
	<info>
		<revision>20/05/2008</revision>
	</info>
	<texts>
		<section-home-developers>For developers</section-home-developers>
		<section-home-developers-text>eyeOS introduces a new way of developing web applications with the eyeOS Toolkit, a class library to help the application development and a group of functions to interactuate with the system. Forget about HTML, JavaScript, User Management, FileSystem and much more. Introduce yourself at eyeOS Development Team today, eyeOS is Open Source Software! [a dev]Go to developers community...[/a]</section-home-developers-text>
		<section-home-discover>Discover eyeOS</section-home-discover>
		<section-home-quicktour>eyeOS 1.6 Gala Quick Tour</section-home-quicktour>
		<section-home-quicktour-1-text>The new eyeOS 1.6 Desktop introduces dozens of usability improvements. With a restyled eyeOS wallpaper, a new common actions bar and some new icons on the desktop, aims to be the perfect default web desktop for everyone.</section-home-quicktour-1-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-1-title>The new Desktop</section-home-quicktour-1-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-2-text>With the new flash based upload system you will be able to select as many files as you want at once and see with a live progress bar how are they being uploaded. Combine this with the new Synchronization system for Windows, Mac and Linux and you will have a permanent backup of your local system, always available from Internet.</section-home-quicktour-2-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-2-title>Improved upload system</section-home-quicktour-2-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-3-text>The new eyeOS 1.6 introduces the drag and drop feature on all the files based applications: drag and drop your private files to user groups, to the trash or between your private folders. You can do it with single files or whole folders.</section-home-quicktour-3-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-3-title>Drag and drop</section-home-quicktour-3-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-4-text>eyeOS 1.6 introduces some new applications such as the completely rewritten eyeFeeds, which will keep you always updated with your favorite news sources.</section-home-quicktour-4-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-4-title>RSS Reader</section-home-quicktour-4-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-5-text>You can now start your spreadsheets and save them as OpenOffice sheets or Microsoft Excel sheets. With an eyeOffice-ready server, you will be able to create new spreadsheets and edit your favorite ones from the improved eyeSheets.</section-home-quicktour-5-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-5-title>New eyeSheets</section-home-quicktour-5-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-6-text>You can launch some new widgets that come by default on eyeOS 1.6 from the Accessories menu in the applications dock. Mini Messages, Calendar and Home will keep you updated about your incoming messages, your today&#039;s events from your calendar and the used quota on your account.</section-home-quicktour-6-text>
		<section-home-quicktour-6-title>Desktop widgets</section-home-quicktour-6-title>
		<section-home-quicktour-back>Back</section-home-quicktour-back>
		<section-home-quicktour-forward>Forward</section-home-quicktour-forward>
		<section-home-quicktour-see>See full tour</section-home-quicktour-see>
		<section-home-taketour-concept>The concept</section-home-taketour-concept>
		<section-home-taketour-download>Download eyeOS 1.6!</section-home-taketour-download>
		<section-home-taketour-welcome>Welcome</section-home-taketour-welcome>
		<section-home-users>For users</section-home-users>
		<section-home-users-text>eyeOS is a new kind of Operating System, where everything resides on a web browser. With eyeOS, you will have your desktop, applications and files always with you, from your home, your college, your office or your neighbour&#039;s house. Just open a web browser, connect to your eyeOS System and access your personal desktop and all your stuff just like you left it last time.</section-home-users-text>
		<section-home-whatis>What is eyeOS?</section-home-whatis>
	</texts>
</lang>
