<lang>
	<info>
		<revision>20/05/2008</revision>
	</info>
	<texts>
		<section-tour-back>Back</section-tour-back>
		<section-tour-next>Forward</section-tour-next>
		<section-tour-text-1>[h3]The new Desktop[/h3]The new eyeOS 1.6 Desktop introduces dozens of usability improvements. With a restyled eyeOS wallpaper, a new common actions bar and some new icons on the desktop, aims to be the perfect default web desktop for everyone.</section-tour-text-1>
		<section-tour-text-10>[h3]eyeOS Mobile[/h3]Remember that you can login to every eyeOS system on the world by tipping its URL followed by /mobile/ from your mobile phone. You will be able to read office files from your hand, see and upload photos from your mobile to eyeOS, and much more.[br /][br /]Welcome to eyeOS 1.6!</section-tour-text-10>
		<section-tour-text-2>[h3]Improved upload system[/h3]With the new flash based upload system you will be able to select as many files as you want at once and see with a live progress bar how are they being uploaded. Combine this with the new Synchronization system for Windows, Mac and Linux and you will have a permanent backup of your local system, always available from Internet.</section-tour-text-2>
		<section-tour-text-3>[h3]Drag and drop[/h3]The new eyeOS 1.6 introduces the drag and drop feature on all the files based applications: drag and drop your private files to user groups, to the trash or between your private folders. You can do it with single files or whole folders.</section-tour-text-3>
		<section-tour-text-4>[h3]RSS Reader[/h3]eyeOS 1.6 introduces some new applications such as the completely rewritten eyeFeeds, which will keep you always updated with your favorite news sources.</section-tour-text-4>
		<section-tour-text-5>[h3]New eyeSheets[/h3]You can now start your spreadsheets and save them as OpenOffice sheets or Microsoft Excel sheets. With an eyeOffice-ready server, you will be able to create new spreadsheets and edit your favorite ones from the improved eyeSheets.</section-tour-text-5>
		<section-tour-text-6>[h3]Desktop widgets[/h3]You can launch some new widgets that come by default on eyeOS 1.6 from the Accessories menu in the applications dock. Mini Messages, Calendar and Home will keep you updated about your incoming messages, your today&#039;s events from your calendar and the used quota on your account.</section-tour-text-6>
		<section-tour-text-7>[h3]New default game: eyeTetravex[/h3]Finally eyeChess, the default game that appeared on eyeOS 1.0 has a colleague: eyeTetravex is the new default game that will keep your whole server addicted with its Highscores features that will beat you to make better results in less time against all the users on the system.</section-tour-text-7>
		<section-tour-text-8>[h3]New Utilities[/h3]Both Calculator and Text Editor have been rewritten to provide a much better functionality. The new Text Editor, for example, includes code highlighting for the most known programming languages including eyecode, with autocomplete for the most known functions.</section-tour-text-8>
		<section-tour-text-9>[h3]Improved System Preferences[/h3]eyeControl has also some noticeable improvements, specially for the system administrator. The new system administration panel has been divided in tabs to improve its usability and be able to expand the available options for future releases.</section-tour-text-9>
		<section-tour-title>eyeOS 1.6 Tour</section-tour-title>
	</texts>
</lang>
