<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<!-- This document is licensed under the Creative Commons 3.0 BY-NC-ND License
	 available at http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc-nd/3.0/. -->
<info>
	<type>Widget</type>
	<general>
		<name>Imagebox</name>
		<name>Image</name>
		<name>Picture</name>
		<tags>
			<tag>widget</tag>
			<tag>friend</tag>
		</tags>
		<shortDesc>An image that can send signals to the system.</shortDesc>
	</general>
	<name>Imagebox</name>
	<description>Imagebox is the widget thought to display an image, also giving the option to specify a signal every time the image is clicked.</description>
	<generic_keys>
		<key>
			<name>name</name>
			<desc>Unique name given to the widget.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>father</name>
			<desc>Parent element inside of which the widget is created.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>horiz</name>
			<desc>Specifies whether its horizontal coordinate must be taken from the left (0) or the right (1) border of its father element. Default value is 0 (left positioning).</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>vert</name>
			<desc>Specifies whether its vertical coordinate must be taken from the upper (0) or from the bottom (1) border of its father element. Default value is 0 (upper positioning).</desc> 
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>x</name>
			<desc>Specifies the horizontal displacement inside its father element, in pixels. Default value is 10 pixels.</desc> 
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>y</name>
			<desc>Specifies the vertical displacement inside its father element, in pixels. Default value is 10 pixels.</desc> 
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>cent</name>
			<desc>
			Specifies how the widget should be centered. Possible values are:
			 0: no centering. This is the default value.
			 1: center both horizontal and vertically.
			 2: center horizontally.
			 3: center vertically.
			 4: place the widget at the horizontal and vertical center of its container element.
			 5: place the widget at the horizontal center of its container element.
			 6: place the widget at the vertical center of its container element. 

			Please note the difference between options 1-3 and options 4-6. Options 1-3 calculate the size of the widget to ensure that the center of the widget is placed at the central point of its container, while options 4-6 set the central point coordinates as the widget's position, thus making the widget displaced from the central point.
			</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>visible</name>
			<desc>Sets the widget visibility. Possible values are 0 (hidden) or 1 (visible). Default value is 1.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>width</name>
			<desc>Sets the width of the widget, in pixels. Default width is 200 pixels.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>height</name>
			<desc>Sets the height of the widget, in pixels. Default height is 200 pixels.</desc>
		</key> 
		<key>
			<name>disableMsg</name>
			<desc>Specifies if the Imagebox must send a signal to the system when clicked. The default value of 0 allows it to send a signal, while any other value prevents it.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>signal</name>
			<desc>Name of the signal sent to the system every time the Imagebox is clicked. In case this key is not specified, the name of the Imagebox will be used instead.</desc>
		</key>
	</generic_keys>
	<specific_keys>
		<key>
			<name>url</name>
			<desc>Using the extern service, specifies the URL of the image.</desc>
		</key>
		<key>
			<name>alt</name>
			<desc>Sets the message displayed when the image cannot be loaded.</desc>
		</key>
	</specific_keys>
	<methods>
		<method>
			<syntax>addEvent(string $eventName, string $eventFunc[, string $args = ''])</syntax>
			<desc>Makes the system execute a given JavaScript code every time certain event of this widget is triggered.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>eventName</name>
					<desc>Name of the JS event. Examples: onchange, onmouseup.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>eventFunc</name>
					<desc>JavaScript code inside the function of the event.</desc>
				</arg>
				<arg>
					<name>args</name>
					<desc>Arguments passed to the function of the event.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>addFriend(object $friend)</syntax>
			<desc>Adds to the friend widgets list of the Imagebox the given widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>friend</name>
					<desc>Friend widget.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>hide()</syntax>
			<desc>Makes the widget invisible.</desc>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>remove()</syntax>
			<desc>Removes this widget, along with its child widgets.</desc>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>setCss(array $params)</syntax>
			<desc>Sets CSS atributes to a widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>params</name>
					<desc>Specifies, in the form of an associative array, the CSS attributes to be applied. Both the key and value of each element must be valid CSS properties and values respectively.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>setHeight(int $height)</syntax>
			<desc>Changes the height of the widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>height</name>
					<desc>New height, in pixels.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>setUrl(string $url)</syntax>
			<desc>Changes the URL of the Imagebox.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>url</name>
					<desc>URL of the Imagebox.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
		 	<syntax>setWidth(int $width)</syntax>
			<desc>Changes the width of the widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>width</name>
					<desc>New width, in pixels.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>setX(int $x)</syntax>
			<desc>Changes the horizontal position of the widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>x</name>
					<desc>New X coordinate.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>setY(int $y)</syntax>
			<desc>Changes the vertical position of the widget.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>y</name>
					<desc>New Y coordinate.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
<method>
			<syntax>show(int $noserialize=1)</syntax>
			<desc>Draws the widget in the screen, allowing to serialize the instance in the session.</desc>
			<arguments>
				<arg>
					<name>noserialize</name>
					<desc>Specifies whether the Imagebox must be serialized or not. The default value of 1 does not serialize it, while a value of 0 does.</desc>
				</arg>
			</arguments>
		</method>
		<method>
			<syntax>unhide()</syntax>
			<desc>Makes the widget visible.</desc>
		</method>
	</methods>
</info>
